New York State Board of Mediation Case Files 5103
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Al-463 Evans Bros. Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Al-472 1511-21 Sheridan Avenue, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Al-473 Atlas China Co. Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Al-474 Long Island Outfitting Co., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Al-476 A. Flohr Company, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Al-478 Abe Schneider, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Al-482 1165 West Farms Road, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Al-485 Croyden Bake Shop, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Al-486 Automatic Woven Wire Supply Co. Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Al-488 Vet Trading Company, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Al-492 3138 Bailey Avenue, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Al-498 1463-65 Boston Road, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Al-499 36-38 West Gun Hill Rd., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Al-501 1590 West 8th Street, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Al-502 601 West 26th Street, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Al-503 Marchese Bakery, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Al-506 Tyler-Made Co. Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Al-516 Union Furniture Co., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Al-517 Alex Tayler & Co, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Al-518 Unique Optical Co. Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Al-520 1173 Nelson Ave Corp, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Al-524 The Carlisle Upholsterers, Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Al-533 2081 Davidson Avenue, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Al-535 3415 Knox Place, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Al-536 4308 Broadway, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Al-541 Charles Furniture Co. Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Al-544 1755 Ocean Parkway, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 83)
- Al-547 Mr. Sol Ashenazy, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 84)
- Al-548 M & W Upholsterers, Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Al-554 2770-2780 Kingsbridge Terrace, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 86)
- Al-564 Window Cleaners Association, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 87)
- Al-570 Lenox Specialty Shop, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 88)
- Al-572 Oakland Parlor Frame Co, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 89)
- Al-577 564-570 Lenox Avenue, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 90)
- Al-581 American Zyloptic Co. Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 91)
- Al-584 Radio City Bar & Grill, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 92)
- Al-600 Avon Upholstering Co., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 93)
- Al-604 Louis Gold Optical Co. Inc., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 94)
- Al-605 Pur-All Paint Co., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 95)
- Al-606 321 West 44 Street, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 96)
- Al-608 Friedland Fixtures, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 97)
- Al-613 62 East 182nd Street, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 98)
- Al-616 777-783 Fox Street, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 99)
- Al-617 1360-70 Merriam Avenue, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 100)
- Al-619 1665 Macombs Road, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 101)
- Al-622 Childs, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 102)
- Al-623 Commercial Carle Co., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 103)
- Al-624 Gleitsman's, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 104)
- Al-626 New York Daily News, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 105)
- Al-627 Breakstone Dairy, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 106)
- Al-633 Krischer Metal Products Corp., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 107)
- Al-634-Al-660 Ar-Kay Meat Market, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 108)
- M-1554 Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- M-1370 Tri-Borough Transportation Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- M-1367 National Can Corp, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- M-1366 Regal Shoe Company, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- M-1361 Brooklyn & Long Island Livery Assn. Inc., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- M-1355 Crawford Clothes, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- M-1412 Kramer Auto Radiator Corp., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- M-1410 Stationary Engineers, Firemen, Maintenance & Bldg Service Union, Local 670, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- M-1405 France Sporting Goods Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- M-1402 Richter, I, Truck Rental Company, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- M-1401 Storms, H. M. Co., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- M-1399 R. K. Baking Corp., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- M-1397 Marseilllaise French Baking Co., Inc., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- M-1395 Ace Leather Goods Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- M-1382 La Rosa, V., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- M-1381 Curley's Clothing, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- M-1376 Kemp & Beatley, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- M-1375 Steel, S. W. & Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- M-1374 Fulton Operating Corp., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- M-1579 Publishers Assn. of New York City, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- M-1373 Block, J. H. & Co., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- M-1372 Germel Operating Corp., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- M-1451 Fur Merchants Employers Council, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- M-1449 Cemetery of the Holy Cross, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- M-1445 Gaspari, J. & Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- M-1446 Tanenbaum, Jerome, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- M-1437 Stern Bros., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- M-1430 Allied Hat Mfgrs. Assn., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- M-1427 Beer, William J., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- M-1426 Alvin Friedberg Inc., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- M-1415 New York Pest Control Assn., Inc., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- M-1548 Associated Hotel & Residence Clubs, Inc., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- M-1537 Fairchild & Sons Inc., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- M-1535 Macy, R. H. & Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- M-1514 Green-Wood Cemetery, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- M-1509 Brady Transfer & Storage Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- M-1507 De Martini Macaroni Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- M-1506 Milady's, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- M-1503 Stromeyer & Arpe, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- M-1499 Brandt Theatres, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- M-1497 Millinery Retailers Assn. Of Greater New York, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- M-1492 Ronzoni Macaroni, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- M-1483 Elks Scene, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- M-1475 Slipper Manufacturers Assn of NY, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- M-1473 Franklin's Millinery Shop, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- M-1470 Zamaz Mfg. Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- M-1467 Superior Optical Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- M-1464 Kolonics & Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- M-1560 Hill Lalin, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- M-1570 Seligman & Latz, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- M-1578 Manhattan Club, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- M-1588 Sudar Manufacturing Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- M-1552 Coward Shoe Co., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- M-1550 City Service Clearning Contractors Inc., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- M-1567 Gutenstein & Lasden, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- M-1557 Publishers Assn. of NYC, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- M-1597 Macy, R. H. & Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- M-1600 Brooklyn Standard Bag Corp., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Cromwell Silver Mfg. Corp, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Corona Corporation, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Confectionery & Tobacco Jobbers Assn. Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Astor Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- J. Abramson & Sons, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Accurate Shoe Company, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Display Well, Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Kings County Cigarette Service, Inc., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Square Hardware Company, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Fink Baking Corp., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  1938
- Englander Spring Bed Company, Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- European Radio Company, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- United Parcel Services, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Dynamic Radio Company, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- United Parcel Service, Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Penner Electric Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Du Wel Cleaning Company, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- David's Fifth Avenue, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Estate of A. Damsky, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Crown Drug Store, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Automatic Day Bed Company, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Philip Ashel P & A Silk Store, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Ascot Wine & Liquor Store, Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Anchor Cleaning Service, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- American Toy Company, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- American Merchandise Company, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- William Amberg, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- I. Altman Furniture Co., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Two Arbitrations Alteration Plumbers, Steamfitters, and Helpers, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- All Brands Tire Exchange, Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Bakery and Confectionery International Union of America Local 474, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Engel Bros., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- The Beacon Sales Company, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Bellows & Company, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Bernard's Millinery, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Collier Service Corporation, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Louis Cohen, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Children's Bus Service, Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Greater NY Photo Fin. Assn., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Lisner, D. Company, Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Milch, D. & Sons, Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Collins Stamp MFG. Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- William Greenbaum (American Beef Company), 1938 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Le Winter Radio, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- J. F. D. Manufacturing Company, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Brunner Ritter Company, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Burger & Klein, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Charles Bloomfield, Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Blue Ribbon Syrup Corporation, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Braddock Hotel, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Collier Service Company, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Dorb the Chemist, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Digby Stores, Inc., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- M & H Trucking Co, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- I. Silversmith & Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Aerovox Corporation, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Paper Association of New York, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Alpha Storagehouses, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Display Mannequin, Inc., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Color Tone Photo Service, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Carroll Silk Stores, Inc., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Canada Dry Ginger Ale, Inc., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Burndy Engineering Company, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Bronx Coffee Company, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Brause Brothers, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Bluestone Photo Print Co., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Blacharsky, Samuel, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Bigelow-Sanford Co, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- B & G. Corporation, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Morris Best, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- H. Baron & Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- California Grape Products, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Barclay Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Baltic Shoe Company, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Jack Babitz Arrex Pharmacy, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Accurate Shoe Company, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Fairchild Aerial Camera Corp., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Eastern Wine Company, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- East Side Metal Spinning & Stamping Co, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 79)
- Digby Stores, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 80)
- Detroit Furniture Dist. Corp., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 81)
- The Crystal Cab Corporation, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 82)
- Crescent Shoe Company, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 83)
- Consolidated Smoked Fish Company, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 84)
- Consolidated Brooklyn Retail Pharmacists, Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 85)
- Commercial Window Cleaning Company, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 86)
- Brooklyn Daily Eagle, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 87)
- Alabama Pipe Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 88)
- Amalgamated Drink, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 89)
- Angle Bed Spring Co., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 90)
- Army & Navy Distributing Co. Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 91)
- Arrow Radio, Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 92)
- Associated Bedding Mfrs. Of Greater New York, inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 93)
- Camron Dairy Products, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 94)
- Central Provision Company, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 95)
- Challenger Utilities Company, Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 96)
- Charles Charcowsky, Inc., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 97)